[
  {
    "name": "Radiohead Live 2018",
    "id": "radiohead",
    "theme": "green",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Yesterday I woke up ...",
        "options": [
          "Thinking about you",
          "With a terrible headache",
          "Sucking on lemon",
          "Did I?"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "2+2 = 5",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "I want ...",
        "options": [
          "A perfect body",
          "A perfect soul",
          "You to notice",
          "When I'm not around"
        ],
        "answer": [
          0,
          1,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "What was the original name of Radiohead?",
        "options": [
          "On A Friday",
          "Mondays",
          "Pink Floyd",
          "On a gloomy day"
        ],
        "answer": [0]
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select-item",
        "question": "If I could be ...",
        "options": [
          "A millionaire",
          "Who I wanted",
          "Who you wanted",
          "Your vacuum cleaner"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "You and ",
        "answer": "Whose army?"
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "In which county was Radiohead founded?",
        "options": [
          "Hong Kong",
          "United Kingdom",
          "New York",
          "San Francisco"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "How many years later from its first appearance was True Love Waits officially release?",
        "min": 1,
        "max": 30,
        "answer": 21
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "She's running out ...",
        "answer": "Again"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "This is what you'll get when you ...",
        "options": [
          "Don't listen to your mom",
          "Mess with us",
          "Mess with the Corleone Family",
          "Don't listen to your heart"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "Queen Live Aid 1985",
    "id": "queen",
    "theme": "yellow",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Who is the drummer of the band?",
        "options": [
          "Travis Barker",
          "Roger Taylor",
          "Just Bieber",
          "Ringo Starr"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "When was the first Queen album released?",
        "options": [
          "1975",
          "1981",
          "1971",
          "1973"
        ],
        "answer": [3]
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "What was their name before Queen?",
        "options": [
          "On Friday",
          "Smile",
          "The Beatles",
          "Just Bieber"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {"type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "What's Freddie Mercury's real name?",
        "options": [
          "Justin Bieber",
          "Madona",
          "Farrokh Bulsara",
          "Bulsara Farrokh"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "Is this the real life or is this just fantasy?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "How many albums have they released?",
        "min": 0,
        "max": 20,
        "answer": 15
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "Is Queen the best band ever?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Who is your favorite silhouetto?",
        "options": [
          "Scaramouch",
          "Bismillah",
          "Beelzebub",
          "Gallileo"
        ],
        "answer": [0,1,2,3]
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "I want to ...",
        "options": [
          "Break free",
          "Get a cheeseburger",
          "Bite the dust",
          "Keep myself alive"
        ],
        "answer": [0]
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "I'm in love with ...",
        "options": [
          "My bike",
          "Myself",
          "My car",
          "Justin Bieber"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "The Beatles on Ed Sullivan",
    "id": "beatles",
    "theme": "blue",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "John Lennon was murdered",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select-item",
        "question": "Here comes ...",
        "options": [
          "Barack Obama",
          "The sun",
          "The end of the world",
          "My son"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "The Beatles were formed in the United States",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "What was the name of the first album of The Beatles?",
        "start": "",
        "answer": "Please Please Me"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Hey Jude, ...",
        "options": [
          "Don't make it sad",
          "Won't take it lad",
          "Don't make it bad",
          "Could you move your car a little?"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Na",
        "options": [
          "Na",
          "Na-na-na",
          "Na"
        ],
        "answer": [
          0,
          1,
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "John Lennon murderer?",
        "options": [
          "Mark David Chapman",
          "Nietzsche",
          "John Lennon",
          "David Mark Chapman"
        ],
        "answer": [0]
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "In which year did the Beatles release their first album?",
        "min": 1950,
        "max": 1975,
        "answer": 1963
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Nobody ever loved me ...",
        "options": [
          "Like you do",
          "Like she does",
          "Like my mom does",
          "Like my dog does",
          "Like I do"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Which two were NOT members of The Beatles?",
        "options": [
          "John Lennon",
          "Paul McCartney",
          "Ringo Starr",
          "Syd Barrett",
          "George Harrison",
          "Madona"
        ],
        "answer": [
          3,
          5
        ]
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "Linkin Park Live 2017",
    "id": "linkinpark",
    "theme": "red",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "Name of the debut album of Linkin Park",
        "start": "",
        "answer": "Hybrid Theory"
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "In The End it doesn't really matter",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "Brad Delson was planning to become a lawyer before founding the band",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "Which year did Chester Bennington join Linkin Park?",
        "min": 1995,
        "max": 2003,
        "answer": 1999
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Which two albums were NOT released by Linkin Park?",
        "options": [
          "Ok Computer",
          "Hybrid Theory",
          "Living Things",
          "One More Light",
          "AM",
          "Meteora",
          "Minutes To Midnight"
        ],
        "answer": [
          0,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select-item",
        "question": "One thing that I don't know why ...",
        "options": [
          "I am so lazy",
          "It doesn't even matter how hard you try",
          "It doesn't even matter how hard you cry",
          "Does it matter if you ever try"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select-item",
        "question": "Who cares if one more light goes ou? ...",
        "options": [
          "Well, I do",
          "Don't give up",
          "You are loved",
          "You got this"
        ],
        "answer": [0]
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "The most viewed song of Linkin Park?",
        "answer": "Numb"
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Which two are members of Linkin Park?",
        "options": [
          "Alex Turnen",
          "Mike Shinoda",
          "Thom Yorke",
          "Jonny Greenwood",
          "Mark Hoppus",
          "Madona",
          "Joe Hahn"
        ],
        "answer": [
          1,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Who left Linkin Park in 1998?",
        "options": [
          "Tom Delogne",
          "Nick Wakefield",
          "Mark Sloan",
          "Mark Wakefield"
        ],
        "answer": [3]
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "Pink Floyd Live In Venice",
    "id": "pinkfloyd",
    "theme": "purple",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Select the ones who are NOT members of Pink Floyd",
        "options": [
          "David Gilmour",
          "Roger Waters",
          "John Deacon",
          "Syd Barrett",
          "Brian May",
          "Nick Mason"
        ],
        "answer": [
          2,
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "In which city was Pink Floyd formed?",
        "answer": "London"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "How I wish",
        "options": [
          "I was a punk rocker",
          "You were here",
          "I could see you",
          "I'd never been born at all"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "The dream is gone, I have become ...",
        "options": [
          "So numb",
          "Emotionally numb",
          "Comfortably numb",
          "Numb"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "How long is Shine On Your Crazy Diamond including all parts?",
        "min": 6,
        "max": 30,
        "answer": 26
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "Open your heart",
        "end": "I'm coming ",
        "answer": "home"
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "'Animals' was Pink Floyd's 10th studio album",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "We don't need ...",
        "options": [
          "No Education",
          "To finish this test",
          "To try",
          "No thought control"
        ],
        "answer": [
          0,
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Last Pink Floyd album Roger Waters appeared on?",
        "options": [
          "The Final Cut",
          "Animals",
          "The Dark Side OF MOON",
          "The Wall"
        ],
        "answer": [0]
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "To hear the softly spoken ...",
        "answer": "magic spell"
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  }

]
